marketingblogonline.com 2013-01-28

# Privacy Policy @ Marketingblogonline.com

**Privacy Policy for www.marketingblogonline.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by [emailHighly-targeted Opt in List. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/building-a-highly-targeted-opt-in-list.html) at choirultw@gmail.com.

At [www.marketingblogonline.com](http://www.marketingblogonline.com/ "Online Marketing Bloggers"), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.marketingblogonline.com and how [itTraining for IT Certification. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/training-certification.html) is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.marketingblogonline.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes [internetNiche markets to super affiliate . Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/how-to-become-a-super-affiliate-in-niche-markets.html) protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.marketingblogonline.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our [advertisingSocial Network Advertising. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/social-network-advertising.html) partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our [advertising5.11 Tactical Boots. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/511-tactical-boots.html) partners include [GoogleStrategic Position in Placement Adsense. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/strategic-position-placement-adsense.html) [AdsenseStrategic Position in Placement Adsense. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/strategic-position-placement-adsense.html), Widget Bucks, Adbrite, Amazon, .

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and [linksLinkadage trade links services. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/linkadage-links-services.html) that appear on www.marketingblogonline.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.marketingblogonline.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.marketingblogonline.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie [managementPPC Bid Management. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/maximum-website-promotion-through-ppc-bid-management.html) with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective [websitesRSS website advantages. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/the-advantages-of-rss-websites.html).

 **Advertising**

This [blogA Money-Making Blog Components. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/money-making-blog-components.html) accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, [paidBest paid review services (1). Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/paid-review-services-1.html) insertions or other forms of compensation. The owner(s) of this [blogAre You Passionate About Your Blog?. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/passionate-blog.html) is compensated to provide opinion on [productsTips for how marketing self products through internet. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/tips-marketing-products-internet.html), [servicesLinkadage trade links services. Read more ... »](http://marketingblogonline.com/linkadage-links-services.html), websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own.

Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest. To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org
